Hello everyone and welcome to this video. Today I want to approach a topic I
haven't done so far with this focus because today I'm going to do mini skirt
only outfits. So I tried to find all the mini skirts in my wardrobe and I had to
search a bit and yeah took some tops and also have new shoes. I think I'm going to
do like four to five outfits and it's going to be colorful and all black lots
of different materials so have fun since I'm not very colorful dressed yet I'm
going to start with this bright green skirt and I do like this one very much
That was fast. I'm just kidding. So first outfit I combined the green with black again because otherwise it would be too colorful. We don't want that.
Of course it's always a good option to combine mini skirts with over knee boots. That way I also do feel more dressed. So there's another plus point.
and today I tried some different kind of feels. They're like ponte and no plateau and I've also
the perms version. Thanks to UpToStep for gifting me these shoes by the way. I'm curious how they
look with the other outfits but yeah for this skirt I think these boots are perfect. Also I
tend to always have a look at the color of the metal parts or accessories so we have silver here
silver here and silver here i wouldn't combine a top or something with gold now so
stay with one color and yeah mini skirts are short
Okay, I want to change back to black and let's stay with PVC. So I'll change. Give me a second.
So all black as promised. It looks very elegant together with the over-knee boots
and that everything is black. Again I stuck with the silver, oh no, it's the only silver accessory here
and a zipper because this jacket has a black zipper. But yeah, it's not a dress. It may look
like a dress but actually I'm layering here. It's a skirt and a jacket and this belt and underneath
second I'm wearing a corset so you won't notice it actively but I think it makes a better figure
like passively wearing corset underclothing I don't think that there's an official mini skirt
length or something I don't know when would you consider a skirt mini like is this too long
probably I don't know the green one was way shorter I don't know so if this is not a miniscule
to your definition I'm sorry but I still wanted to show this outfit all right I don't want to
bore you with all black for the next outfit so I'm going to add color again so there's no black
in this outfit except for the shoes and let me be clear I would not go out wearing this
because it's way too colorful and I don't know I ordered this bodysuit like a while ago or one
year ago or something and was like yeah I can try to combine it with the skirt but I knew from the
beginning that it's like a video or picture look and not something I would wear in my daily life
and sorry if i look like i just woke up here's one life hack don't put on turtleneck tops
after doing your hair it's always a pain in the ass and it's always ruining your hair and your
makeup i don't know but i think it gives some kind of 80s vibes with the holographic skirt and this
snake print bodysuit it's a fun outfit it does look good with my hair I don't think I
would have liked that much with the red hair so yay the necessary praise for my blue hair in this
video check but yeah I think I'll switch back to another black outfit this is the
like gothic clubbing outfit with the corset and the miniskirt all black PVC
again I paired it with the ovni boots because I thought they are going to look
better with this combination and I think they do. So yeah this is definitely mini skirt. I can't
really turn around without showing my booty and as we all know YouTube does not like
close-up recordings of booties because apparently that's not good for children. I don't know.
Fun fact, I got YouTube videos of mine demonetized before the whole channel went down
because I had close-up recordings of my bum in them.
There is a lot of free space here going on in my shoulders
because it's like an overbust corset and I have no shrug or something.
So I filled the space with this oversized statement piece choker with a huge moon.
So there's at least something going on here and it doesn't look too empty.
One last outfit with a red mini skirt and again the skater cut.
And I have to say I prefer this cut over this like straight A cut whatever.
But yeah I like this outfit nevertheless.
I wanted to pair this top with a red skirt but it didn't look good.
So I took this black skater skirt and combined it with the top and I think this looks awesome.
It's again like a dress lookalike.
So I put the skirt under the top here.
Looks like one.
And together with the perms it looks really elegant.
And yeah, I don't know.
I didn't plan this but it looks good.
Okay, I can't really do good periods with these shoes. Anyway, our last outfit. So this is definitely the last outfit. Red mini skirt and after the fiasco with the overbust, no, with the corset top, I did try this. A loose fitting band shirt. I put a knot in it.
I almost said less than four words.
And yeah, I think it's a total inconsistency of style together with the shoes.
But it's somehow pretty cool.
Together with the hairstyle it reminds me a bit of like schoolgirl style.
Anyway, so it's comfortable. It is not too tight.
And this is like a really cool outfit to just chillax.
I hope you had fun with this video.
What was your favorite style?
Tell me in the comments.
And I think mine was...
I don't know.
I like this one, but I also like the all black outfits.
I have to see the pictures and the video material.
And I think then I can decide.
And I write it down in the description text.
anyway check out my instagram and my patreon if you want to support this channel and have a nice
day bye